Zoe: I had the experience of working
with a child with autism who really
enjoyed anything related to messy play.
And through messy play, we were able
to help them to learn to communicate
through asking for different items,
and it was always a lot of fun.
It was always very messy.
I'd always be covered in whatever it
was they were interested in - from
like flour, to hot chocolate powder,
marshmallows, whatever it was.
Paint anything.
And it was always great fun, and it
really helped the student to learn how
to communicate because they got a lot of
enjoyment out of it, and they were always
very excited to  engage in anything messy